choosenissan.com 2019-05-20

# Nissan Legal Privacy Policy | Nissan USA

Nissan may use third party providers to collect and record data on the use and performance of our websites during your visit (“Usage Data”), which may include without limitation the pages you view, the search terms you enter, your IP address, and personal information that you submit through the website. Usage Data may be collected by Nissan or its third party provider through “cookies”, log files and other technology. Nissan uses this information to administer its websites and to improve the services provided to you. Nissan may share information collected through our websites with suppliers to provide services for us or as required by law or court order. Nissan may also share Usage Data in an aggregate statistic format with a third party; such statistics would not include personal information. Nissan does not rent, sell, or trade Usage Data outside of Nissan.

Nissan may not respond to “do not track” beacons, tags or other such signals including browser-based prompts or controls. You may also receive tracking mechanisms from other parties prior to visiting our websites that will continue to track your activity while on our websites. Such data would be subject to the privacy policy of the other party from whom you received the mechanism, and we do not control or receive data from such mechanisms. For more information on how to manage advertising controls including tracking mechanisms, please visit [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personal information, until a user provides that information (see below). If a user rejects or deletes the cookie, he/she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to receive notification of special offers, or participate in any contests that may take place. Cookies also enable us to track and aggregate clickstream behavior data. By doing this we can better target the interests of our users and enhance their experience on our site.

Nissan also maintains standard web logs that record data about all visitors to our websites. These logs may contain:

  * The Internet domain from which you access the website.
  * Your IP address (Your computer is automatically assigned an IP address when you surf the Internet. Your IP address is either static or dynamic. A static IP address may be identifiable to you; a dynamic address is usually not identifiable to you.)
  * The type of browser and operating system you use.
  * The date and time you visited the website.
  * The pages you viewed on the website.
  * The address of the website from which you linked.

Nissan uses web log and clickstream information to help us design our site, to identify popular site features and to make the site more useful for visitors. Web logs are recorded in sequential files, and we normally do not attempt to identify individuals from these logs. However, we may use web logs to identify persons attempting to break into, disrupt, or damage our Site. We may share web log information with law enforcement personnel if we believe evidence exists, or is likely to occur, of a violation of federal, state or local laws or regulations.

Nissan advertising at other non-Nissan sites may be serviced by Nissan service providers, who may use cookies to collect information about your visits to those sites. Information collected may include the pages visited, date and time, browser information and/or IP address. We normally make no attempt to link this information to you personally, except under circumstances described above. This information is gathered in order to help us customize and target our advertising to the needs and interests of our customers. If you wish to opt out of this tracking at our advertising at third party sites, please visit the following sites:
